Guide to the Yale University Press Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1910-1979; Accession 1990-A-042
  - Columbia University Press, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - D, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Doob, Leonard W., 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - E, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - East West Center Press -- University of Hawaii, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Editorial Department Memos, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Employment, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - F, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Fitts, Dudley, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Benjamin Franklin Series Correspondence, 1961-1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - G, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Governing Board, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Guinzburg, Thomas H. -- The Viking Press, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - H, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Holden, Reuben A., 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Harvard University Press, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Gene Hawes Correspondence re: Handbook, comp copies, etc., 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Heckscher, August, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - History Department Correspondence (with Messrs. Lamar, Blum, etc.), 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - I, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - J, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Josephy, Alvin M. Jr., 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - K, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Chester Kerr's trip re: Vinland Map, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - L, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Landsverk, O.G., 1966-1971 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Lehmann -- Haupt: Gutenberg (Correspondence, etc.), 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Local History Conference, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Lipson, Leon, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Liverpool University Press --Mr. John G. O'Kane, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Lewis, W.S. and (Lewis and Hofer Correspondence), 1958-1968 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Lybrand, Ross Brothers and Montgomery, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - M, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - McGill University Press -- Robin Strachan, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Mohawk Paper Company, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Memos to the staff, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - N, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - National Science Foundation, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - New Haven Free Public Library, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Northwestern University Press -- Mr. Robert P. Armstrong and others, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - New York Times, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - O, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Oxford University Press, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - P, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Q, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - R, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Messrs. Ritchie and Prown re: Art Gallery and Garvan College, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - S, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Shakabpa, Tsepon Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Singer: Works of Trumbull, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - School Mathematics Study Group, 1961-1968 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Stands in Timber correspondence with Margot Liberty and others, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Sturtevant, Mrs. Theda Maw, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Stanford University Press -- Mr. Leon E. Seltzer, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - T, 1968-1968 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Tucker, Carll Jr., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - U, undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - U.S. Publishers Association, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - University of Texas Press, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - V, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Von Mises; Ludwig -- Human Action, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - W, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Waters -- Taylor Correspondence, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - X-Y-Z, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Yale Review, 1962-1968 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Yale University Press --60th Anniversary Dinner, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - A, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Agee: Permit the Voyage, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - American Heritage, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Andenaes, Tomes, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - American Book Publishers Council, Inc., 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - American University Press Services (AUPS), 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Association of American University Presses, Inc. (AAUP), 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Athearn, Robert G., 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - B, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Baker, Houston Correspondence, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Black, Cyril E. re: Vernadsky, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Blanck: BAL, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Brewster, Kingman Jr. and Mrs., 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Bowles, Chester, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Brown, J. Trevor and Mrs., 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Bucher, Francois, 1963-1970 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - C, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - China Trading Corporation, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Columbia University Press, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - D, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Department Heads, Memos to, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Drob, Leonard W., 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Dugan, Mr. and Mrs. Alan, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - E, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Economic Growth Center, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Editorial Department, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Eisenman, Alvin, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Employment, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - F, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Committee of Finance Memos, etc., 1963-1969 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Fitts Festival, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - G, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Governing Board, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Financial Forecast, 1969-1974 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Graef, John, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - H, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Hammacher Schlemmer, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Harvard University Press, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Holden, Reuben A., 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - I, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Ingstad, Helge - correspondence, 1960-1967 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - J, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - K, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Kerr, Chester - correspondence re: trip to England, Morocco, Thailand, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Kerr, Chester - Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Kerr, Chester - trip to Munich, London, Oslo, Bergen, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Kerr, Chester - trip to London, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Kerr, Chester correspondence re: trip to London, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Kerr, Chester correspondence re: trip to Dublin, London, Seville, Madrid, Frankfurt, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Kubler - Crosby - Herbert correspondence re: History of Art Department matters, 1965-1969 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - L, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Labaree, Leonard W., 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Lada-Mozarski, Valerian, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Lange, Dorothy - American Exodus (Oakland Museum Correspondence), 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Lederberg, Joshua (Silliman Lecturer), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Lee, The Honorable Richard C., 1967 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth S., 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Lord, Poems on Affairs of State, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Luce Papers, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Luncheons, Dinners and Receptions, 1965-1970 (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - M, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Maximilian - Bodmer Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - McCarthy, Senator Eugene J., 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - McConnell, R.A., 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - McDougall Papers - The Long Lost Papers of George Washington, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Co. (3M), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Memos to the Staff, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - N, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - National Foundation on Arts and Humanities, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - New Haven Free Public Library, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - New Journal, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - O, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - O'Neill Correspondence re: titles with Mrs. O'Neill, Mr. Gallup, Mr. Cerf, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - P, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Princeton University Press, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Committee on Printing and Design Memos etc., 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Pierson, George W., 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Committee on Publications Memos etc., 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Philipson, Morris et al - correspondence re: CCY, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Q, undated (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - R, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Robinson: Black Studies in the University, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - Rogers, Rutherford - Sterling Memorial Library, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - Rosenthal, Arthur J. Basic Books, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 171)
  - Rouse, Irving and Michael Coe correspondence re: Publication in Anthropology, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 172)
  - Routledge and Kegan Paul Ltd., 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 173)
  - Rundell, Walter, Jr., 1967 (Box 4, Folder 174)
  - Ryskamp, Charles - The Pierpoint Morgan Library, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - S, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 176)
  - Saarinen, Mrs. Eero and other correspondence re: Saarinen, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - Saturday Review, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - Schulman, Jack - Cambridge University Press, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 179)
  - Seltzer, Leon E. - Stanford University Press, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - Skelton, R.A.: Magellan's Voyage, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 181)
  - Skelton, R.A.: Pigafetta Manuscript, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 182)
  - Sloan, John - Prints Correspondence, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Smith, Morgan K. - Riverside Press, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Sterling Memorial Library - Correspondence with Tanis, Ottemiller, Rogers, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Strong: English Icon, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - T, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Taylor, Charles H., Jr., 1965-1970 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Terhune, A. McKinley, 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - U, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Universitetsforlaget (University of Oslo) - Ulla Wellestrand and Edward Aslaksen, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - University of Chicago and University of Chicago Press, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - University of Montreal - University of Montreal Press, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - University of Texas Press, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - University of Toronto Press, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 196)
  - University of Wisconsin Press, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 197)
  - V, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 198)
  - W, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 199)
  - Walker, Charles A - Berkeley College, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - Weaver, Howard S., 1965-1970 (Box 5, Folder 201)
  - Wellington, Harry H., 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 202)
  - Wilder, Mitchell A. - Amon Carter Museum of Western Art, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 203)
  - Wilson, O. Meredith - University of Minnesota Press, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 204)
  - Wilson, Thomas J. - Atheneum Publishers, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 205)
  - Wolfe: Milton IV, 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 206)
  - Wroth: Verrazzano Voyages, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 208)
  - XYZ, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 209)
  - Yale Daily News, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 210)
  - Yale University News Bureau, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 211)
  - Yale university press Ltd. Including C - Y - McG, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 212)
  - Journal - March, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 213)
  - Journal - May, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 214)
  - Deposits made on 6/12, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 215)
  - Journal - Cash 1/31, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 216)
  - Deposit - April, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 217)
  - Deposit - February, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 218)
  - Journal - Cash December, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 219)
  - Acheson, Dean G., 1937 (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Adams, Frederick B., Jr., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Adams, James Truslow, 1930-1932 (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Adams, Thomas S., 1917 (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Agee, James, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - Aiken, Alfred, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Albers, Josef, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Allen, F. Sturges, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Alloway, Henry, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - American Library Association, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Andrews, Charles M., 1929-1938 (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - Andrews, E., 1915 (Box 6, Folder 232)
  - Angell, James R., 1917-1938 (Box 6, Folder 233)
  - Armstead, George B., 1930 (Box 6, Folder 234)
  - Arnold, Thurrnan, 1937-1940 (Box 6, Folder 235)
  - Arrow Editions, 1933-1936 (Box 6, Folder 236)
  - Avery, Edward S., 1915 (Box 6, Folder 237)
  - Babb, James T., 1938 (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - Bacon, Benjamin W., 1932 (Box 6, Folder 239)
  - Bailey, George T., 1922-1941 (Box 6, Folder 240)
  - Baker and Taylor Company, 1911-1916 (Box 6, Folder 241)
  - Barnes, John H., 1926 (Box 6, Folder 242)
  - Baur, P.V.C., 1915 (Box 6, Folder 243)
  - Bean, Donald P., 1929 (Box 6, Folder 244)
  - Becker, Carl, after 1932 (Box 6, Folder 245)
  - Benet, Stephen Vincent, 1918-1955 (Box 6, Folder 246)
  - Benet, Wilfiam Rose, 1917-1919 (Box 6, Folder 247)
  - Berenson, Bernard, 1929-1930 (Box 6, Folder 248)
  - Bevis, Palmer, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 249)
  - Biddle, Alfred, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 250)
  - Bingham, Hiram, 1913-1968 (Box 6, Folder 251)
  - Blake, Henry T., 1936 (Box 6, Folder 252)
  - Bliss, Charles F., 1938 (Box 6, Folder 253)
  - Bliss, Robert Woods, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 254)
  - Blodgett, Delos A., 1925 (Box 6, Folder 255)
  - Blossom, Dudley S., 1938 (Box 6, Folder 256)
  - Book and Quill Lending Library and Bookshop, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 257)
  - Book Publishers Code, 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 258)
  - Bolton, Chester C., 1938 (Box 6, Folder 259)
  - Borchard, Edwin M., 1937 (Box 6, Folder 260)
  - R.R. Bowker Company, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 261)
  - Brown, Cyril, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 262)
  - Brown, J. Trevor, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 263)
  - Boyden, James W., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 264)
  - Buck, Howard S., 1917 (Box 6, Folder 265)
  - Buckland, E.G., 1915 (Box 6, Folder 266)
  - Burpee, Charles, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 267)
  - Boulton, Eugene, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 268)
  - Brooks, Charles S., 1917 (Box 6, Folder 272)
  - Brooks, Henry S., 1918 (Box 6, Folder 273)
  - University of Buffalo, New York, 1917-1934 (Box 6, Folder 274)
  - Burrows Brothers Company, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 275)
  - Cable, George W., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 276)
  - Calhoun, Reverend Newell M., 1912-1916 (Box 6, Folder 277)
  - University of California Library, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 278)
  - University of California Press, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 279)
  - Canadian American Relations Series, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 280)
  - Canby, Henry S., 1932-1938 (Box 6, Folder 281)
  - Cape, Johnathan and Harrison Smith, Inc., 193? (Box 6, Folder 282)
  - Cardogo, Benjamin W., 1938 (Box 6, Folder 283)
  - Carnegie Endowment Fund, 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 284)
  - Chamberlain, Sir Austen, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 285)
  - Chamberlain, Samuel, 1933-1938 (Box 6, Folder 286)
  - Chappell, F. Valentine, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 287)
  - Chaplin, Charles, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 288)
  - Chester, Colby, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 289)
  - Childs, Marquis W., 1934-1938 (Box 6, Folder 290)
  - Chidsey, Donald Harr, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 291)
  - Chinese National Association of the Mass Education Movement, 1932-1938 (Box 6, Folder 292)
  - Chisholm, High, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 293)
  - Chittenden, Russell H., 1939 (Box 6, Folder 294)
  - Chrysler, Walter P., Jr., 1931 (Box 6, Folder 295)
  - Clapp, F.M., 1915-1916 (Box 6, Folder 296)
  - W.B. Clarke Company, 1910-1913 (Box 6, Folder 297)
  - Claudel, Paul, 1915-1930 (Box 6, Folder 298)
  - Claudel's The Hostage: Professor Colliard - Research on above translation, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 299)
  - Coleman, R.V., 1925-1928 (Box 6, Folder 300)
  - Columbia University Press, 1931-1937 (Box 6, Folder 301)
  - Colum, Padriac, 1923-1926 (Box 6, Folder 302)
  - The Commonwealth Fund, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 303)
  - Connecticut Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 304)
  - Cornell University Press, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 305)
  - Cortissoz, Royal, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 306)
  - Crosby, M r s. Raymond M., 1917 (Box 6, Folder 307)
  - Cross, Wilbur L., 1911-1966 (Box 6, Folder 308)
  - Crowell, Hon. Benedict, 1920-1923 (Box 6, Folder 309 - 310)
  - Cunningham, Frank S., 1935-1937 (Box 6, Folder 311)
  - Cushing, D r. Harvey, 1925-1929 (Box 6, Folder 312)
  - Cutten, Dr. George., 1935 (Box 6, Folder 313)
  - Dana, Arnold, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 314)
  - Dana, J. Dwight, 1926-1936 (Box 6, Folder 315)
  - Danford, Robert M., 1917 (Box 6, Folder 316)
  - Darlington, Ralph, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 317)
  - Davidson, Eugene, 1930-1958 (Box 6, Folder 318)
  - Davis, Howard L., 1929 (Box 6, Folder 319)
  - Day, Benjamin (grandfather), 1929-1938 (Box 6, Folder 320)
  - Day, Clarence, 1933-1938 (Box 6, Folder 321 - 322)
    General
    Folder 322 not in box as of September 8, 2017.
  - Day, Mrs. Clarence, 1936-1939 (Box 6, Folder 323)
    File not in box on September 8, 2017.
  - Day, Clive, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - Day, George Parmly - Personal, 1914-1941, 1952-1959 (Box 6, Folder 325 - 326)
  - Day, George Parmly and Yale University Press, 1911-1938 (Box 6, Folder 327 - 330)
  - Day, Wilhelmine (Mrs. G.P. Day), 1919-1926 (Box 6, Folder 331)
  - Day, Julian, 1933-1940 (Box 6, Folder 332)
  - Day, Sherman, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 333)
  - Denison, Robert C., 1913 (Box 6, Folder 334)
  - Dawing, Arthur S, 1914 (Box 6, Folder 335)
  - Dodd, Lee Wilson, 1932-1933 (Box 6, Folder 336)
  - Donaldson, Norman V., 1928-1959 (Box 6, Folder 337)
  - Dostoyewsky, Aimee, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 338)
  - Duke University Press, 1925-1929 (Box 6, Folder 339)
  - Dunn, R.G. and Co., 1926 (Box 6, Folder 340)
  - Dwight, Timothy, Reverend, 1914 (Box 6, Folder 341)
  - Eisenmann, Alvin, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 342)
  - Ellsworth, William W., 1936 (Box 7, Folder 343)
  - Elizabethan Club, undated (Box 7, Folder 344)
  - Ernbree, Edwin R., 1912-1939 (Box 7, Folder 345)
  - C.A. Esty Paper Company, 1917-1918 (Box 7, Folder 346)
  - Fairchild, Fred R., 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 347)
  - Evarts, Sherman, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 348)
  - Edgarton, Franklin, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 349)
  - Farnam, Thomas W., 1925-1932 (Box 7, Folder 350)
  - Farrand, Max, 1909-1918, 1935-1966 (Box 7, Folder 351 - 352)
  - Farwell, John V., 1938 (Box 7, Folder 353)
  - Faunce, W.H.P., Dr., 1926 (Box 7, Folder 354)
  - Felthousen, E.G., 1926 (Box 7, Folder 355)
  - Fenton, Charles, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 356)
  - Fergusson, Percy, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 357)
  - First Church of Christ in New Haven, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 358)
  - Fleischner, Charles M., 1931-1941 (Box 7, Folder 359)
  - Fletcher, Sir Angus, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 360)
  - Fitzgerald, William B., 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 361)
  - University of Florida Press, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 362)
  - Florida State Historical Society
    - 1926-1927 (Box 7, Folder 363)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 7, Folder 364)
    - 1931 (Box 7, Folder 365)
    - 1932 (Box 7, Folder 366)
    - 1933 (Box 7, Folder 367)
    - 1934 (Box 7, Folder 368)
    - 1935 (Box 7, Folder 369)
    - 1936 (Box 7, Folder 370)
    - 1937 (Box 7, Folder 371)
    - 1938 (Box 7, Folder 372)
    - 1939 (Box 7, Folder 373)
    - 1940 (Box 7, Folder 374)
    - 1941-1943 (Box 7, Folder 375)
    - 1944-1949 (Box 7, Folder 376)
    - 1933-1953 (Box 7, Folder 377)
  - Follett, Wilson, 1926-1929 (Box 7, Folder 378)
  - Fox, Dixon Ryan, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 380)
  - Francis, David R., 1912-1913 (Box 7, Folder 381)
  - Frankfurter, Felix, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 382)
  - French, Robert Dudley, 1929-1938 (Box 7, Folder 383)
  - Furniss, Edgar, 1938-1944 (Box 7, Folder 384)
  - Furniss, Edward S., 1929 (Box 7, Folder 385)
  - Gabriel, Ralph, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 386)
  - Gardner, Helen, 1917 (Box 7, Folder 387)
  - Garvan, Francis P., 1925-1934 (Box 7, Folder 388)
  - Gates, Gilman, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 389)
  - Gerard, James W., 1917 (Box 7, Folder 390)
  - Geyse, F.H.V., Mrs., 1917 (Box 7, Folder 391)
  - Gillett, James, Captain, 1926-1934 (Box 7, Folder 392)
  - Girodie, Andre, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 393)
  - Goodhart, Howard, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 394)
  - Goodyear, A. Conger, 1926-1935 (Box 7, Folder 395)
  - Goodyear, William H., 1912-1917 (Box 7, Folder 396)
  - Grandin, G.W., 1938 (Box 7, Folder 397)
  - Grandin, Thomas, 1930-1934 (Box 7, Folder 398)
  - Graphic Arts Institute of Massachusetts, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 399)
  - Graves, Henry S., 1932 (Box 7, Folder 400)
  - Graydon, Thomas, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 401)
  - Green, Ernest M., 1939 (Box 7, Folder 402)
  - Grimes, Mrs. George, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 403)
  - Griswold, Whitney, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 404)
  - Guggenheim Foundation, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - Hackett, E. Byrne, 1911-1929 (Box 7, Folder 406)
  - East Haddam Connecticut Library, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 407)
  - Hadley, Arthut Twining, 1914-1931 (Box 7, Folder 408)
  - Haldane, John S., 1916 (Box 7, Folder 409)
  - Halsey, Ralph W., 1937 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - Haley, Margaret, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 411)
  - Hambridge, Jay, 1917-1941 (Box 7, Folder 412 - 417)
  - Hannam, William H., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 418)
  - Hapwood, Mrs. Norman, 1929-1937 (Box 7, Folder 419)
  - Harkness, Edward S., 1929-1938 (Box 7, Folder 420)
  - Harvard University Press, 1929-1938 (Box 7, Folder 421)
  - Heckscher, August, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 422)
  - Herring, Hubert, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 423)
  - E.L. Hildreth Company, 1912-1918, 1923-1936 (Box 7, Folder 424 - 427)
  - Hill, Clyde M., 1936 (Box 7, Folder 428)
  - Hifles, Frederick, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 429)
  - Hinckley, Henry Barrett, 1917 (Box 7, Folder 430)
  - Hodgson, Ralph, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 432)
  - Holland, Nelson, 1925 (Box 7, Folder 433)
  - Hoover, Herbert, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 434)
  - Johns Hopkins University Press, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 435)
  - Hotchkiss School, Lakeville CT, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 436)
  - Horne, David, 1954-1965 (Box 7, Folder 437)
  - Hosford, Hester E., 1924 (Box 7, Folder 438)
  - Buebsch, B. W. (publisher), 1910-1916 (Box 7, Folder 439)
  - Hutchinson, Eliot, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 440)
  - Ihlder, John, 1916-1917 (Box 8, Folder 441)
  - Irving, John D., 1917 (Box 8, Folder 442)
  - Japan Paper Company, 1913-1917 (Box 8, Folder 443)
  - Jennings, Annie B., 1930-1938 (Box 8, Folder 444)
  - Johnson, Allen, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 445)
  - Jones, R. Alfred, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 446)
  - Journal of the American Oriental Society, 1917-1919 (Box 8, Folder 447)
  - Journal of Biblical Literature, 1917-1920 (Box 8, Folder 448)
  - Judson, Arthur, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 449)
  - Judson, Junius, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 450)
  - Keller, Albert G., 1930-1937 (Box 8, Folder 451)
  - Kelley, J. Frederick, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 452)
  - Kendall, William Sergeant, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 453)
  - Kennedy, E.R., 1918 (Box 8, Folder 454)
  - Kent, Albert E., 1933 (Box 8, Folder 455)
  - Keogh, Andrew, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 456)
  - Kerr, Chester, 1958-1963 (Box 8, Folder 457)
  - Kifborne, Robert S., 1937 (Box 8, Folder 458)
  - Kimball, Arthur Reed, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 459)
  - Kingsbury Family, 1917-1929 (Box 8, Folder 460)
  - Knollenberg, Bernhard, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 461)
  - Knopf, Alfred A., 1926-1940 (Box 8, Folder 462)
  - Kohut, Alexander, Mrs., 1926-1940 (Box 8, Folder 463)
  - Labaree, Leonard, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 464)
  - Laski, Harold, 1925-1933 (Box 8, Folder 465)
  - Charles Lauriat Co., 1912-1915 (Box 8, Folder 466)
  - Lehman, Eugene, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 467)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth S., 1937-1965 (Box 8, Folder 468)
  - Limited Editions Club, 1933-1937 (Box 8, Folder 469)
  - Lippmann, Walter, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 470)
  - Little, Brown and Company, 1913-1916 (Box 8, Folder 471)
  - Lloyd George, David, 1916-1917 (Box 8, Folder 472)
  - Lohman, Helen, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 473)
  - Low, Benjamin R.C., 1916 (Box 8, Folder 474)
  - Lowell, Amy, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 475)
  - MacCracken, Henry, 1913-1917 (Box 8, Folder 476)